Simo Mordi

(206) 354 - 2053 | simo.mordi@gmail.com | LinkedIn / GitHub - SimoMordi

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I aim to revolutionize the tech industry one customer experience at a time. With over a decade in the fast-paced, profitdriven world of hospitality, I specialize in delivering excellent customer service, managing difficult situations, and building long-lasting relationships. Fueled by curiosity and ongoing tech education, I'm poised to merge these skills into impactful tech roles. My goal is to transition the excellent customer service skills and time-sensitive tasks I've honed into creating better experiences in the evolving tech industry.

Skills: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, MongoDB, Git, Express, AWS, Development tools

Languages: English, French, Arabic

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Craft Studios Seattle, WA

Software Engineer Aug 2023 - Present

- Collaborated with a group of developers to enhance our code and increase website usage
- Designed a web platform that doubled user engagement and simplified the checkout experience with automated calculations.

Princeton Brightworks Duvall, WA

Web Developer and Co-Founder

Aug 2022 - Present

- Completed advanced courses to quickly adapt new skills, resolving maintenance issues 30% faster.
- Developed a full-stack website featuring a responsive and dynamic interface, boosting user engagement by 200% and increase response time

KONA Grill Plano, TX

Bartender Oct 2021 - Apr 2022

- Oversaw busy bar operations, keeping customer wait times under 3 minutes during peak hours
 - Delivering excellent customer service especially in difficult situations, and building long-lasting relationships

Din Tai Fung Bellevue, WA

Server Oct 2019 - Mar 2020

- Maintained a high level of attention to detail while serving customers, resulting in a 99% error-free order rate
- Acquired in-depth menu knowledge to increase sales by 20% through recommendations and pairings.

Marriott International Seattle, WA

Bartender Dec 2013 - Nov 2019

- Boosted drink sales by 20% by innovating a diverse cocktail menu, blending new and classic flavors
- Implemented creative marketing strategies to promote the new cocktail menu, leading to a 30% increase in customer engagement and repeat business

Hyatt International hotels

Seattle, WA

Bartender Feb 2009 - Dec 2013

EDUCATION

PerScholas Seattle, WA

Software Engineering Bootcamp, full-stack developer
Graduation Date: Nov 2023

University of Hassan II Casablanca

Economics

Institute Specialized Technology Inter-Enterprise

Electrical and Mechanical Engineering

Casablanca, Morocco

Casablanca, Morocco

Graduation Date: 2005